A Guide to the Dottie Schick Collection of Political Memorabilia, 1926-2004 (bulk 1968-2002)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Dottie Schick Collection of Political Memorabilia, 1926-2004 (bulk 1968-2002)
The Library of Virginia
42676
22.75 cu. ft. (68 boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Adolph Schick, 18 April 2006.
Biographical Information
Dorothy (Dottie) Schick (1930-2005) was the daughter of Bertha and Albert Wasserman of Arlington, Virginia. The Wasserman's owned the landmark Al's Motors, the oldest Chrysler-Plymouth dealership in Northern Virginia. Dottie Schick graduated from Washington and Lee High School, received her bachelor's degree from the University of Oklahoma, and studied at the Corcoran College of Art and Design. Mrs. Schick was a longtime Northern Virginia Democratic activist and served as a member of the Democratic National Committee and chairwoman of the Fairfax Democratic Committee. For 38 years, Dottie and her husband, Adolph (Sonny) Schick, hosted the annual Mason District Democratic Committee Crab Feast, attended by hundreds of elected officials, candidates, lobbyists, and supporters. Guests ranged from former presidents Jimmy Carter and Bill Clinton to former governors Charles S. Robb and L. Douglas Wilder, along with many local officials and candidates.
Scope and Content
Collection, 1926-2004 (bulk 1968-2002), of Dottie Schick, longtime Northern Virginia Democratic activist. Throughout her career in politics, Mrs. Schick collected a variety of Democratic artifacts and memorabilia. The bulk of the collection includes materials collected during her tenure, 1968-2004, although she collected materials dating to 1926. The collection includes campaign brochures and posters, correspondence, inaugural invitations and programs, Democratic Committee and Democratic Party of Virginia convention materials, photographs, publications, and scrapbooks. Also included are numerous artifacts including bumper stickers, campaign buttons, commemorative coins, lapel pins, hats, and pens. Campaign materials are included for Leslie Byrne, Jimmy Carter, Bill Clinton, Dwight D. Eisenhower, Henry Howell, John F. Kennedy, George McGovern, Harold Miller, J. Sargeant Reynolds, Charles Robb, Franklin Roosevelt, Mary Sue Terry, Harry F. Truman, Mark Warner, and L. Douglas Wilder, among others. Although the majority of the collection relates to the Democratic Party, included are some artifacts and papers relating to the Republican Party.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Papers, 1926-2004
Series II. Campaign Buttons, 1937-2004
Series III. Artifacts, 1963-2002
Series IV. Bumper stickers, ca. 1970-2000
Series V. Clippings, 1976-1992
Series VI. Oversize, ca. 1970-2000
Series VII. Scrapbooks, 1968-1992
Contents List
- Series I. Papers, 1926-2004., Extent: 27 boxes. (Box 1-24)
  Papers, 1926-2004, including campaign and inauguration papers, convention materials, correspondence, directories, invitations, newsletters, photographs, and publications. The papers mainly consist of campaign and inauguration papers for various local and national political figures and are arranged alphabetically by last name of politician. The campaign and inauguration papers include biographies, correspondence, committee lists, inaugural invitations and programs, newspaper clippings, press releases, publications, and resumes. Papers relating to Presidential campaigns include those of Harry S. Truman, Dwight Eisenhower, John F. Kennedy, Lyndon Johnson, Jimmy Carter, Walter Mondale, Michael Dukakis, Bill Clinton, Al Gore, and John Kerry. Papers relating to local campaigns include those of Gerald Baliles, Henry Howell, Henry MacKall, Dorothy McDiarmid, John Melnick, Andrew Miller, Harold Miller, John Milliken, J. Sargeant Reynolds, Charles Robb, Mark Warner, and L. Douglas Wilder.
  Also included are brochures, invitations, guides, programs, official proceedings, and tickets, from conventions held by the Democratic Party of Virginia and Democratic National Committee. Minutes, committee lists, finances, and reports relating to the Democratic Party of Virginia are also included, as well as The Fairfax County Democrat newsletters, 1972-1989.
  The correspondence, 1968-1998, mainly includes campaign letters asking for Mrs. Schick's support or thanking her for her support, purchase of tickets and comments about the Crab Feast, and candidates announcing bids for election. Included are letters from many prominent local and national politicians. Photographs include presidential and local inaugurations, Crab Feasts, campaign fundraisers, and miscellaneous political figures. The collection also includes several programs, 1970-1990, from Jefferson-Jackson Day dinners held by various chapters of the Democratic Party of Virginia.
  Of note are Dottie Schick's campaigns for Democratic National Committeewoman, including announcements, correspondence, clippings, flyers, and resumes. Also of note are the attendees lists, clippings, flyers, guest book, tickets, photographs, and invitations for the Mason District Crab Feasts and Schick Seafood Extravaganza, 1973-1996.
  Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Allen, George, 1994. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Inauguration of Governor George F. Allen, Lieutenant Governor Donald S. Beyer, Jr., and Attorney General James S. Gilmore, III.
  - Bagley, Dick, 1984. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Campaign for Governor.
  - Baliles, Gerald, 1985-1988. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Baliles, Gerald, 1986. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Campaign for Governor Gerald Baliles, Lieutenant Governor L. Douglas Wilder, and Attorney General Mary Sue Terry.
  - Baliles, Gerald, 1986. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Inauguration as Governor.
  - Baliles, Gerald 1986. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Baliles, Gerald, 1986. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Baliles, Gerald, 1986. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Beyer, Donald S., 1989-1990. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Campaign and inauguration for Lieutenant Governor.
  - Byrd, Harry F., Jr., 1970. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Campaign for U.S. Senate.
  - Byrne, Leslie, 1987-1996. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Campaigns for House of Delegates and Lieutenant Governor.
  - Carter, Jimmy, 1977-1980. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Campaign and inauguration as President of the U.S.
  - Clinton, William J. and Albert Gore, Jr., 1992. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Campaign and inauguration as President and Vice President of the U.S.
  - Clinton, William J. and Albert Gore, Jr., 1992. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Clinton, William J. and Albert Gore, Jr., 1993-2000. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1958-1990. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1978. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1980. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1982. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1983. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1984. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1985. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1986. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1987. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1988. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1991. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1994. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1995. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1996-1998. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Christmas cards, 1990s. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 2004. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, undated. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Cuomo, Mario, 1985. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Washington Roasts Mario Cuomo.
  - Davis, Richard J. 1981-1985. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1936. (Box 3a)
    Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
  - Democratic National Convention, 1972. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Miami, Florida
  - Democratic National Convention, 1980. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    New York, New York
  - Democratic National Convention, 1984. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    San Francisco, California
  - Democratic National Convention, Official proceedings, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Democratic National Committee, Calendar, 1986. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1987-1988. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Miscellaneous membership lists and statements.
  - Democratic National Convention, 1988. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Atlanta, Georgia
  - Democratic National Convention, 1988. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1988. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1988. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1988. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1988. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1988. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1988. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1988. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Democratic National Convention, Official proceedings, 1988. (Box 5)
  - Democratic National Convention, Clippings, 1988. (Box 5a)
  - Democratic National Convention, Clippings, 1988. (Box 5b)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1989-1991. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1992. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Democratic National Convention, Official proceedings, 1992. (Box 6)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1992. (Box 7)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1992. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1996. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Chicago, Illinois
  - Democratic National Committee, Calendar, 2000. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Committee officers, Alexandria district, 1970. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Committee officers, Annandale district, 1969-1984. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Committee officers, Arlington district, 1970-1985. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Committee officers, Centreville district, 1969-1984. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Committee officers, Dranesville district, 1971-1984. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Committee officers, Fairfax district, 1977-1984. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Committee officers, Lee district, 1969-1983. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Committee officers, Mason district, 1971-1984. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Committee officers, Mount Vernon district, 1969-1983. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Committee officers, Providence district, 1969-1984. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Committee officers, Springfield district, 1969-1983. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Contributor lists, undated. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Convention, 1981. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Convention, 1982. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Convention, 1984. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Convention, 1985. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Convention, 1988. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Convention, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Delegates, 1982-1984. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Democratic Leadership Council, 1986-1988. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Directory of Elected Officials, 1971-1983. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Fairfax County Democratic Committee, 1984-1995. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Mason District Committee, 1974. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Membership lists, undated. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Miscellaneous, 1982-1985. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Northern Virginia Democratic Club, 1977-1978. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, State Central Committee Meeting, 1988. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, State Finance Committee, 1972-1975. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, Tenth District Committee, 1978-1992. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Dukakis, Michael, 1988. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Campaign for President of the U.S.
  - DuVal, Clive L., II, 1969. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Campaign for Virginia House of Delegates.
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1953. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Program and ticket for inauguration as President of the U.S.
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1957. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Program for Inauguration Ball as President of the U.S.
  - Gore, Al 2000. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Hobson, Richard, c. 1976. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Howell, Henry, 1969. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Campaign for Governor of Virginia.
  - Hudgins, Cathy, ca. 1984. (Box 11, Folder 7a)
    Campaign for National Committeewoman.
  - Invitation and fundraisers, 1960-1970. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Invitations and fundraisers, 1960-1970. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Invitation and fundraisers, 1980-1989. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1988. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Newspaper article.
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Maifest, 1970. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 1971. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 1981 April 12. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 1984 April 28. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 1987 February 7. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 1987 June 13. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 1988 January 30. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 1988 March 29. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 1988 April 9. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 1988. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, 1990 February 10. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines, 1965. (Box 11, Folder 23)
    Inaugural program as President of the U.S.
  - Kennedy, John F., 1959-1963. (Box 12)
    Publications:
    Life Magazine, 1959 August 24; 1962 July 13; 1963 November 29; 1963 December 6.
  - Kennedy, John F., 1963-1988. (Box 13)
    Life Magazine, 1964 February 21; 1964 May 29; 1964 October 1; 1965 July 16; 1965 July 23; 1965 July 30; 1983 November.
    TV Guide, 1963 November 22-25.
    John F. Kennedy Memorial Album.
    The Washington Post: Parade, 1988 July 3.
    Good Housekeeping, 1966 August.
    Newsweek, 1963 December 2.
  - Kennedy, John F., 1963-1967. (Box 14)
    Look, 1963 December 31; 1966 March 22; 1967 January 24; 1967 February 7; 1967 March 7.
  - Kennedy, John F., 1963-1968. (Box 15)
    He Gave His Life.
    Life Magazine, 1963 December 13; 1964 June 19; 1965 January 29; 1968 July 5.
    JFK Memorial Book.
    Post Magazine, 1963 December 14.
    Kennedy and His Family in Pictures.
    John Fitzgerald Kennedy Library.
    Four Days: The Historical Record of the Death of President Kennedy.
    The Torch is Passed.
  - Kennedy, John F. (Box 16)
    A Day in the Life of President Kennedy.
    The Death of a President.
    The Kennedy Wit.
    A Thousand Days.
  - Kennedy, John F., 1960-1964. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Kennedy, John F., Jr., 1999. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, 1994. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Kerry, John, 2004. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kinney, Dave, 1968. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Campaign for U.S. Congress.
  - MacKall, Henry C., 1969. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - McDiarmid, Dorothy, 1969. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - McDonald, undated. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Campaign for Vice-Chairman.
  - McGovern, George, 1972. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Campaign for President of the U.S.; McGovern for President Ecology Coloring Book.
  - Melnick, John, 1969. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Campaign for Attorney-General of Virginia.
  - Miller, Andrew P., 1969-1976. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Campaigns for Attorney General and Governor of Virginia.
  - Miller, Harold O., 1970. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Milliken, John, 1985-1986. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, c. 1980-1990. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Mondale, Walter F., and Geraldine Ferraro, 1984. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Moss, Thomas, c. 1969. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - NARAL, 1990. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Literature.
  - Newsletters, The Democrat,1972-1976. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Newsletters, The Democrat,1980-1981. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Newsletters, The Democrat, 1982-1989. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Newsletters, Miscellaneous, 1986-1991. (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1968. (Box 17, Folder 19)
    The Nixon Yearbook.
  - Notes, undated. (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Peabody, Endicott, 1972. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Campaign for Vice President of the U.S.
  - Photographs, 1980-1981. (Box 18, Folder 1a)
    1981 Democratic Convention (Va. Beach, Va.); Misc.
  - Photographs, 1982-1983. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, 1983. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Fairfax County Democratic Committee.
  - Photographs, 1986. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Inauguration; State Central Committee; Crab Feast; Misc.
  - Photographs, 1987-1988. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Wilder, Beyer, and Terry campaign; Crab Feast; Misc.
  - Photographs, 1988. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Democratic National Convention (Dukakis).
  - Photographs, 1989. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Governor Baliles and Lt. Governor Wilder; Women's Rights Pro-Choice Rally; Misc.
  - Photographs, 1990. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    Inauguration; Martin Luther King Holiday at Israeli Embassy with Ron Brown, chairman of DNC.
  - Photographs, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Inauguration; Ron Brown; Misc.
  - Photographs, 1991-1992. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Democratic National Convention; Crab Feast with Bill Clinton; Misc.
  - Photographs, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Inauguration.
  - Photographs, 1993. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Crab Fest; Mary Sue Terry for Governor.
  - Photographs, 1994. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Charles Robb for Senate; Crab Feast with Charles Robb and Lady Byrd Johnson.
  - Photographs, undated, ca. 1970-1995. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Crab Feast; Charles Robb; Misc.
  - Plum, Ken, undated. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Publications: (Box 20)
    Capital Comics by Bob Brown (1983).
    Know Your Congress (1976).
    The Living White House(1966).
    More Who's in Charge Here? by Gerald Gardner (1962).
    National Directory of Women Elected Officials(1985).
    National Directory of Women Elected Officials(1987).
    A New Spirit, A New Commitment, A New America: The Inauguration of President Jimmy Carter, Vice PResident Walter F. Mondale (1977).
    Our Nation's Capital: Washington, D.C. (1942).
    The People, Press, and Politics(1987).
    A Pictorial History of the United States: Looking Back from Coolidge to Columbus. A Souvenir of the Sesqui-Centennial International Exposition (1926).
    The Scandalous Cartoons of Doug Marlette (1988).
    Seattle Underground by Bill Speidel (1964).
    Stars and Swipes(1988).
    U.S. News Presents The Next President: Exclusive Interviews with the Candidates and Their Wives on the Landmark TV Series With David Frost(1988).
    Virginia Democrats: A Photographic Portrait by Don Patterson (1991).
    While We're Watching Them Look What's Happening Here...The Radical Right is Tightening Its Grip on Congress!(1984).
    Women in Congress 1917-1990.
  - Reynolds, J. Sargeant, 1969. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Road to Richmond Ball, 1996. (Box 21, Folder 1a)
  - Robb, Charles S., 1976-1978. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Campaign and Inauguration for Lieutenant Governor of Virginia.
  - Robb, Charles S., 1982. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Robb, Charles S., 1982. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Inauguration as Governor of Virginia.
  - Robb, Charles S., 1982. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Robb, Charles S., 1982. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Robb, Charles S., 1985. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Northern Virginia Democratic Victory Gala.
  - Robb, Charles S., 1986. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Robb, Charles S., 1987-1989. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Robb, Charles S., 1990-1994. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Robb, Charles S., undated. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1945. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Schick, Dottie, Campaign, 1973-1982. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Schick, Dottie, Campaign, 1984. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Schick, Dottie, Campaign, 1984. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Schick, Dottie, Campaign, 1984. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Schick, Dottie, Campaign, 1988. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Schick, Dottie, Campaign, 1988. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Schick, Dottie, Mason District Crab Feast, 1969-1980. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Guestbook.
  - Schick, Dottie, Mason District Crab Feast, 1973-1992. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Schick, Dottie, Mason District Crab Feast and Schick Seafood Extravaganza, 1992-1996. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Schick, Dottie, Resumes, 1974-1985. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Shriver, Sargent, 1976. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Skallerup, Walter T., 1969. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - State Board for Community Colleges, 1983-1984. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - State Board for Community Colleges, 1983-1984. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - State Board for Community Colleges, 1983-1984. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - State Board for Community Colleges, 1990-1991. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Strawberry Spring Soiree, 1987. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Truman, Harry S., 1949. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Inauguration as President of the U.S.
  - Virginia Legislative Directory, 1978. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Legislative Directory, 1981-1987. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Legislative Directory, 1990-1997. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Voting statistics. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Voting statistics, 1972-1979. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Voting statistics, 1984-1987. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Voting statistics, Fairfax County Election Results, 1974-1976. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - V.O.T.E. Ohio, c. 1978. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Voter registration, undated. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Warner, Mark, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Warner, Mark, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Watts, Vivian, 1979. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Campaign for Committee Chairman.
  - Weinberg, Bob, c. 1990. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Campaign for Congress.
  - Wilder, L. Douglas, 1984. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Campaign for Lieutenant Governor of Virginia.
  - Wilder, L. Douglas, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Wilder, L. Douglas, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Wilder, L. Douglas, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Wilder, L. Douglas, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Wilder, L. Douglas, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Wilder, L. Douglas, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Wilder, L. Douglas, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Williams, Carrington, 1973. (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Series II: Campaign buttons, 1937-2004., Extent: 21 boxes. (Box 25-45)